计时和 JavaScript 这就是我不想说
Timing and JavaScript, this is,
I try not to say which
公司给了我这些问题，因为我和他们谈过很多。
companies gave me these questions, because
there's a lot of them that I've talked to.
但这是一家真正的公司，是一个很大的公司。
But this is a real company,
it's a big one.
这一点都没有帮助
That's not helpful at all.
这是我在时间上所解决的一个真正问题。
This is a real problem that I
have solved before about timing.
但要开始计时
But to start with timing,
如何在 JavaScript中调度内容 ?
what do we know about how to
schedule things in JavaScript?
所以，让我们说我想要每 200 毫秒发生的事情。
So let's say I wanted something
to happen every 200 milliseconds.
在 JavaScript中如何执行此操作 ?
How would I do that in JavaScript?
假设我在 JavaScript中每 200 毫秒都要打印 hello world
Let's say I wanna print hello world
every 200 milliseconds in JavaScript,
我要怎么做
how would I do that?
>> setInterval。 >> setInterval，这是正确的。
&gt;&gt; setInterval.
&gt;&gt; setInterval, that's right.
setInterval在循环之前会发生某种情况，直到您将其取消为止。
setInterval, have something happen
on a loop until you cancel it.
所以如果我说 setInterval ，它会在 x 毫秒后执行一些功能。
So if I say setInterval, it'll execute
some function at x milliseconds.
setTimeout 表示它将等待任何秒数， 500，不管您传入什么，
setTimeout means it'll wait whatever
seconds, 500, whatever you pass in, and
那就能起作用了
then it'll that function.
这就是在 JavaScript中进行计时的两种方法。
So those are the two ways of
doing timing in JavaScript.
我们将讨论请求动画框架
We'll talk about request
animation frame for
但我不想把这些都混在一起
a different sort of timing, but
I didn't wanna mix that up into here.
好吧，那么说时间，什么是借项 ?
All right, so talking about timing,
what is debounce?
> > 这是一种节流的方法，所以你不会做得太多了吧。
&gt;&gt; It's a way to throttle things, so
you don't do it too much, I guess.
> > 嗯，那是正确的，它是一种减缓某些东西的方法。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, that's exactly right,
it's a way of slowing something down.
一个很好的思维方式是自动完成搜索。
A good way of thinking about
debounce is autocomplete search.
我不希望我输入的每个字符都要触发请求。
I don't want every single character
that I type to be firing off requests.
所以如果我打字，我如何变得像杰姆一样高，
So if I'm typing,
how do I become tall like Jem,
那就意味着只要那句是
that means as long as that sentence is,
意思是我每一个请求都要解雇所以我们要去处理
that means I'm firing off every single
request, so we wanna debounce that.
所以我们想把 debunce 设定在 500 毫秒内
So we wanna set the debounce to,
say, 500 milliseconds.
也就是说每当有人停止打字
So that means,
whenever someone stops typing,
那就会被开除了
that's when the debounce is gonna fire.
让我们开始行动
So let's implement debounce.
我不久前才在电话屏幕上找到这个
I actually got this one on
a phone screen not too long ago.
所以我不仅仅是让这些问题难以解决。
So I'm not just making these
questions up to be hard.
这些都是人们所问的真正的问题。
These are real questions that people ask.
这对一个人的理解很有吸引力
And it's a fascinating insight
into someone's understanding,
设定我的 debunce
setting my debounce.
我给你一个提示，你需要 setInterval 或 setTimeout。
I'll give you a hint, you're gonna
need either setInterval or setTimeout.
我可能会用 setTimeout ，但你会做的。
I would probably use setTimeout,
but you do you.